Yes friends, the numbers of MCA Quattro have
come, so we will talk about that
in this video and will know whether you should
invest the cheque can or not. Let's
start, so first of all,
if we talk about dividend here, then the
company has declared a dividend of 17.40 pieces, which
means that if you have a
cold share, then you will
get more than 120 dividends here, which means that
you will get more money there than the sale of one share.
If we
talk about revenue here, then in comparison to the previous cost,
98%, in this way, the number of Binu is
big for the company and this number should be
written on one against 1 crore and you must have seen that the
way the
involvement in the commodity market here increases in this entire quarter, if
we look at the political issues here, then due to that, there is a
lot of trading in commodities like crude oil, gold and silver coins,
because of that, if we talk about the profitability of this company here, then
it is at number 6, a big  This is
on a quarterly basis and see this number
at 81 crores. If we look at the operating
profit, if we talk about it, then the
company's operating profit number is
130 crores. On a quarterly basis,
this number is so low. If we talk about Captain,
first let's talk about the hair oil Vishwa's
number here
and here if we talk about revenue, then
at 10:00, the number of Tere Bin Ji
is big on Hero New Year basis, but the
profitability has fallen by 4% here
and this number is at 1-32 crores.
But if
we talk about the operating profit LED here, then see,
last year in this chapter the company's
operating profit number was 10 crores,
but now the company's operating profit
number is 65 crores.
We are seeing the growth of the painkiller chain at 230 crores here and on this basis, we are
seeing the company's net profit, sorry operating profit, now
you will say that why is the net profit number so
low, if  The reason behind the
company's operating profit of 65 crores and
net profit number of 186 crores will be
decided by the
company. For the quarterly spot market, the
company developed a new software
and for developing that topic, the
company had a one-time accident of
20 crores, due to which the company has earned this net profit
number. If
we look at the operating profit number, there is
chain roti at 230 and this is the
only decrease that is visible and we are
seeing a growth of 35 percent in the company's numbers on American television, so if we
look at the company's
numbers according to net profit, if only the
net profit number is shown in the market or on news channels, then
it is possible that the market may
get negative from this and on Ram Navami, a correction of 10 to 12
Bachchans can be seen in the stock,
but from the long side, there are other
points which if we talk about, definitely
this number is required,
this company on a new topic  If I am flirting
then definitely in the coming time
it will have more new reactions for the company
and the more I will tell you that
net profit margin of 32-40 percent is
seen in the C business, if more
revenue of Rs. 10 crores is
generated there then more profitability of Rs. 10 to 12 crores is
expected there,
so definitely if you see
around 50 crores has already fallen from its voltage,
a good business or it is seen
in the commodity market, if you see the
involvement of people will increase, it appears to be
a dominant player from the middle and
submarine is needed so that it should be on your radar, let me
tell you that from the
C and K numbers of MCA, you must have understood it well,
if you have any queries, please
comment, I will definitely reply to your comment,
thank you friends, you have a
Nike shoe